I believe diversity is what is going to
save humanity it also might be what
tears us apart I asked a question on
Twitter this morning because it was
question I was asking in my own mind
laying in bed waking up if you had to
choose between two worlds
one of which was everybody looks the
same everyone has the same exterior but
in our internal selves are very diverse
and we know that or we all look
completely different but we have the
same internal structure we have the same
emotions the same intelligence the same
capacity and capability and inside right
do we have diverse exteriors or diverse
interiors it's obvious we live in a
world of both but often I think we get
so wrapped up in that we have both of
them that we forget or we don't honor
both of them so in a world that is we
all look the same then looks our next is
your important same assure maybe we wear
different clothes but your hairstyle you
can't really be angry someone's no size
or someone has too big of teeth because
you're all the same unless you're gonna
have augmentation done but your internal
structure you're gonna see okay we have
different capacity for emotional
response we've different capacity people
to tackle complex problems or to be able
to do the physical intelligence things
like playing sports in a world where the
opposite is true where we're all exactly
the same inside but we look different on
the outside then we're going to have the
same capacity for emotion we're gonna
think the same thoughts have the same
we're gonna experience the world
slightly differently because of how the
world treats us if that world treats
people differently because their looks I
think we trinsic lee and logically know
that most of what somebody looks like is
beyond their control without drastic
surgery and so whether your face is
symmetrical whether what color your hair
isn't color your eyes are
are all potentially things you can
change but also
there's a different analysis and ERDs of
beauty that really nobody can obtain but
they're all we're all measured up
against them and which is ridiculous
it's something we have to do away with
we have to start honoring that all beat
bodies are amazing all bodies are
beautiful they don't need to be
beautiful to everyone you don't need to
be attracted to me I don't need to be
attracted to you but that we allow for
the diversity of the external all of our
sizes all of our shapes all of our
colors all of our things we choose to
wear or not wear our diverse and yet so
much of our life depends on what you
look like and how you present in the
world that we almost forget that our
interior world is also diverse that we
have different capabilities of
experiencing emotions we can see that
we're tall and short we can see that
we're bigger and smaller we cannot see
that we're just looking at someone
whether they're quicker to anger whether
they've experienced more grief whether
they what kind of intelligence they have
a college kind of challenges they have
we already hurt people based on what
they look like or don't look like even
the most gorgeous people the society
says is are the ideal beauty are still
hurt by the fact that our world is so
wrapped up in looks I think and yet we
get that it's not important and yet it's
highly important our internal world we
treat as like you have more power here
but I don't think you do just like you
can't change the shape of your nose
about without surgery without drastic
work you can't necessarily change your
emotional states like the the frequency
of having them or the what you do in
them
it'll it's hard in that moment and so I
just this thought this question got me
to thinking about this today and I
thought maybe someone else might also
want to think about it what kind of
world if you had to choose because
someone you know you are chose neither
option on
which it's clearly a hypothetical
question you can't choose neither it's
like a skewed you wanna get ripped apart
by a tiger or a shark clearly the answer
is neither clearly the answer to this is
I don't want to live in a world of
uniformity and looks or in personality
but I want to celebrate the diversity
that we are all of our diversity because
it's already here we might as well
utilize it to create a world that works
for us to create a world that allows
that diversity to feed into the common
good and we all benefit rather than
picking out who should be successful and
allowing them to thrive and everyone
else is look so that's today's video
will again some time a better world's on
its way and we're all going to
participate in creating it thank you